lomaximoproductions.com 2016-11-11

# Privacy Policy – Artists, Latin Music, DJ Mixes, Mixtapes, on IAMLMP.COM

The Lomaximo Productions Corp. (“IAMLMP or Lomaximo Productions”) Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the Terms of Service and other terms and conditions of use which are incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of the Lomaximo Productions Corp. website (“IAMLMP.COM”) and are referred to as the “Agreement” throughout.

Lomaximo Productions Corp. may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your use of the website and any related services (“Services”) indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.

Any Content uploaded by you to Lomaximo Productions Corp. becomes published Content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

Lomaximo Productions Corp. uses IP addresses to measure, analyze, and identify usage and trends, administer the website and collect information for its databases.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Cookies identify you for our database, but provide no information other than that which you have already provided Lomaximo Productions Corp.. You may reject or delete the cookie, however, you may not be able to access your uploaded files if you have not already created an account. Cookies also can enable Lomaximo Productions Corp. to track and target your interests to enhance your experience on our website.

You may review, alter or delete personal information or account information on your Account page.

We have the right to reference and refer to usage of, and relationship with, the Customer or the Customer’s company, which may be determined by the domain used in the registered email account. No press releases shall be made without the written consent of the Customer.

We will not rent, sell or share your personal information with third parties. We may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by United States of America (“USA”) law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to comply with a legal process served on us, protect and defend the rights or property of Lomaximo Productions Corp. or its users, identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties, and cooperate with lawful investigations of destructive activities.

Third-party websites, services, or advertising linked to Lomaximo Productions Corp. are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites or services may collect personally or non-personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. Lomaximo Productions Corp. is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites, advertisers, or companies. You are solely responsible for safeguarding and protecting the secrecy of your password.

Lomaximo Productions Corp. is not responsible if you volunteer personal information online that is accessible to the public. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

If you are not a resident of the USA, you understand and agree that Lomaximo Productions Corp. stores and processes your information on computers located in the USA, any by providing any data to Lomaximo Productions Corp., you consent to the transfer of such information to the USA.

In the event that Lomaximo Productions Corp. is acquired or merged with a third party company or organization, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. In the event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws affecting creditors’ rights, it is possible that Lomaximo Productions Corp. and its officers, owners, employees, agents, information providers and licensors may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used.

Although we intend to protect your personal information within our power, Lomaximo Productions Corp. cannot ensure, warrant, or guarantee the security of any information you add to IAMLMP.COM and you do so at your own risk.

Please e-mail reports of any violations to info@lomaximoproductions.com

Sept 21, 2015
